Mohammadsohil Saiyad

Mobile: 8866745129.

Email ID: sohilsaiyado18@gmail.com

Profile Summary

Dedicated and result-oriented website developer with 4+ years of experience in understanding and anticipating the agile infrastructure needs and creating an environment where development, quality assurance, staging & production work can proceed efficiently and securely.

Work Experience

- 1) Working as a **wordpress developer** at **Sinelogix Technologies Pvt Ltd**, Vadodara, from **Jun 2020 to date**.
- 2) Wordpress developer at Pavans Group Techsoft Pvt Ltd, Vadodara, from Dec 2018 to June 2020.
- 2) Junior php developer at Alian Software Techsoft Pvt Ltd, Anand, from Aug 2017 to Dec 2018.

Key Responsibilities

- In-depth WordPress development experience with high-quality outcomes.
- In-depth understanding of performance/security considerations
- Developing/modifying custom WordPress/Woo-Commerce themes and plugins.
- In depth knowledge of PHP, MYSQL, React, JS, CSS and HTML.
- Comfortable with git-based development and deployment workflow.
- Knowledge of WordPress coding standards.

Skills

- Knowledge in web application development.
- PHP, Wordpress, Woocommerce.
- SQLs writing ability.
- Knowledge in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Strong communication & analytical skills.

Education

2013-16 M.C.A from Shivam Education Campus, Valasan.

2012-14 **B.C.A** from AMCOST College, Anand

Personal Information

Gender : Male

Date of birth : 04/06/1993 Nationality : Indian Marital Status : Married

Languages known : Gujarati, English & Hindi

Permanent Address: Saiyad wada,

At: Sarsa Ta, Dist: Anand,

Gujrat, 388365

Declaration: I hereby declare that all the above information is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place: Anand

Date: M.A.Saiyad